Parul Sharma

Marketing Automation Specialist

Ward No - 3, Batal (125), Himachal Pradesh, 173208, India

✓ sparul247@gmail.com

+919015009656

▼ Portfolio Website

in LinkedIn

GitHub



PROFILE

I have an overall experience of around 3+ years in different industry segments. I have experience in marketing automation, product development and services, supply chain management, planning and team management. Further to enhance my skills in today's data driven AI world, I have good knowledge of Statistics, Data Analysis, Data Visualization, Machine Learning, Deep Learning, and Natural Language Processing.

EDUCATION

2010 - 2014

Baddi, India

2008 – 2010 Solan, India Bachelors of Technology in Electronics and Communication,

Baddi University 🛮

High School, MRA DAV □



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Jan 2020 – present Panchkula, India

Marketing Automation Specialist, Grazitti Interactive ☑ Roles and Responsibilities

- Working dedicatedly on Demand generation programs like Webinars, Product Tours and Sales Demo development.
- Email Engagement programs
- Social engagement programs with Gatted assets for Linkedin, Google, Instagram and other ad websites.
- Working on operational campaigns like Lead Scoring and Data Normalization
- Marketo Instance Audit

Tools used

• Adobe Marketo Engage, ON24, Webex, Litmus, MS-Excel

Oct 2020 – Dec 2020

Panchkula, India

Aug 2020 - Oct 2020

Bengaluru, India

Marketing Automation Intern, Grazitti Interactive

• Worked on the Adobe Marketo Engage , an Adobe's marketing automation tool

Data Science Intern, iNeuron □

• Working as Data Science Intern on a Finance Project.

Aug 2015 - Nov 2016

Bengaluru, India

Support Head - Retail and Handheld Billing Solutions,

Wep Solutions Limited □

Roles and Responsibilities

- Develop support plans to achieve the company's revenue goal and customer satisfaction goals.
- Analyze data to plan the demand and future projections.
- Monitor product failure and quality trends and plan actionable.
- Develop support strategies for customer satisfaction
- Develops support plans and policies for new region development and customer support.
- Travel pan India to meet authorized sales & service partners and end customers regarding post-sales issues, partner meet, and training.
- Handled a team of 12 people across various domains like services, logistics, testing, training, and vendor development.

Apr 2015 – Jul 2015 Bengaluru, India

Product Specialist - Retail Billing Solutions, Wep Solutions Limited ☑ **Roles and Responsibilities**

- Works closely with marketing and R&D teams and finalize the customizations in existing products.
- Conducts the QA, pilot launch, and other tests for new product development.
- Tests the software for any bug and approves the same for final production.
- Travel pan India to meet authorized sales & service partners and end customers regarding product performance reports and also plans their regular training.

Aug 2014 – Mar 2015 Bengaluru, India

Service Coordinator - **Retail Billing Solutions**, Wep Solutions Limited ☑ **Roles and Responsibilities**

- Maintain TAT for service calls
- Plans quarterly spares availability in different service centers
- Provides quarterly corporate training to the Support Team, Sales Managers authorized Dealers and Service providers regarding new product developments and developments in the existing products.



SKILLS

- Demand Generation
 - Bemana Scheration
- HTMLPython
- Seaborn
- Machine Learning

- Email Marketing
- CSS
- Pandas
- Tableau
- Natural Language Processing

- Data Analytics
- MS Excel
- Numpy
- SQL

- Marketing Operations
- Project Management
- Matplotlib
- Deep Learning



LANGUAGES

English

Hindi

Punjabi



Data Science Architecture

from iNeuron

Power BI Masters 🗷

from iNeuron

Deep Learning Master

from iNeuron

Statistics ☑ *from iNeuron*

Tableau Masters 🖸

from iNeuron

INTERESTS

- Learn latest technology trends
- English Grammer
- Play Piano and Guitar

- Indian History
- Indian Constitution